myvortexx.com 2013-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Vortexx on the CW

  1. ## Introduction

 **PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING MYVORTEXX.COM**.

Welcome to www.myvortexx.com, owned by Vortexx Entertainment Ventures LLC (“we,” “our” or “us”). This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) is provided to help ensure a rewarding and transparent online experience for all visitors of this website and any successor website (the “Website”). If you are under the age of 18 (a “minor”), all legal responsibilities under this Policy are assumed by your parent or legal guardian. As such, if you are a minor, please have your parent or legal guardian review and discuss this Policy with you before using the Website

We treat your personal information with care and respect, and are committed to providing a fun, safe and secure Website for people of all ages. This Policy describes our online information practices, including the type of information collected on the Website, our treatment of such information, and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. By using this Website, you and if applicable your parent or legal guardian agree to be bound by this Policy.

For information on the collection of personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13), please see paragraph VII below.

  2. ## The Information We Collect

    1. General Overview of Information Collected By Us: We collect two basic types of information on this Website, personally identifiable information and anonymous information. We only collect personally identifiable information when you provide it to us by participating in certain activities on this Website that require registration, or use social media sites in connection with this Website. When you visit this Website, some of the anonymous information we collect includes, but is not limited to: (1) the current Internet protocol address and the type of computer operating system you are using (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS); (2) the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer); (3) your UDID (for mobile devices); (4) the domain name of your Internet service provider (5) your activities while visiting this Website (e.g., which of our Web pages you viewed or which games you played); and (6) the advertisements you have been shown.
    2. Registration Information: Although registration is optional, we may require you to register to participate in certain Website activities, such as games, online polls, message boards, chat rooms, profile pages, promotion offers, or public forums. The information required to register for these activities may include: (1) first name; (2) last name; (3) birth date; (4) gender; (5) country, state (if applicable), and city of residence; (6) your zip code; (7) user name; (8) login password; (9) telephone number; and (10) other relevant information. We collect this information to help visitors take advantage of this Website’s offerings, respond to visitor’s requests for product services, and improve their overall Website experience.
    3. Social Media Information: The Website may offer or require you to register for, or log into a social media account to participate in certain activities, or permit you to use social media plugins such as Facebook’s “Like” and Google Plus’s “+1” (the “Social Media Sites”). When you use Social Media Sites your username, password, and other available information may be collected. Social Media Sites have their own privacy policies that apply to your use of their services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of Social Media Sites, and as such, visitors should consult Social Media Sites’ privacy policies before using them in connection with this Website.
    4. Contest and Sweepstakes: We may offer visitors of this Website the opportunity to participate in online sweepstakes, contests, and other promotional activities (the “Promotional Activities”). To enter these Promotional Activities you may be required to provide your first and last name, email address, and/or other possibly personally identifiable information. On occasion we may promote Promotional Activities conducted by third parties on their websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such third party websites, and as such, visitors should consult these third party websites’ privacy policies before participating in such Promotional Activities.
    5. Electronic Newsletters: Visitors may have the opportunity to receive email newsletters and promotions from us and our business affiliates. To take advantage of this feature you will have to provide us with your email address. Please note, you may unsubscribe from these email newsletters and promotions at anytime by clicking the unsubscribe link in the emails we send you.
    6. Wireless Marketing: In accordance with local law, appropriately aged visitors may have the opportunity to register for special promotions, services, programming and information delivered via text messaging and/or wireless devices. In order to participate in wireless marketing services, you will have to fill out a registration form by providing your telephone number, email address, cell phone carrier’s name, and other possibly personally identifiable information, or send a text message to a telephone number designated by us. 

By registering or participating in wireless marketing services you acknowledge, understand, and agree that you will be charged by your wireless carrier for all messages you receive from us and send to us. Standard messaging rates will apply, unless noted otherwise. Under no circumstances will we be responsible for any wireless, email or text message charges incurred by you, or by a third party that had access to your wireless device, telephone, or email address.

    7. Location Information: We may collect and store information about your precise geographic location. You may be able to prevent sending us your location information by changing the settings on your computer or mobile device.
  3. ## How We Collect Your Information

When you visit this Website, we automatically collect certain information from your computer or mobile device. This Website uses software called cookies, web beacons, and/or similar technologies (collectively referred to as “Tracking Technologies”) to collect such information. Cookies are small text files placed in visitors' computer browsers when they visit a website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Although cookies could enable us to relate a visitor's use of our Website and the internet to personal information that the visitor has provided, such as an e-mail address, we do not use cookies in connection with personal information, except to ensure that visitors under the age of thirteen (13) provide a parental email address in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior of visitors and collect data about their use. For example, web beacons can be used to count the number of web page visitors or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a web page visitor. We, our third party service providers, and/or our partners use web beacons on our Website from time to time for this and other purposes.

We use Tracking Technologies to help tailor our content, determine how many visitors we have and how often they visit various sections of this Website, and to improve and customize content. We, our third party service providers and/or our partners may also use Tracking Technologies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on this Website. This helps us provide visitors with relevant advertising.

By visiting this Website, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge, understand, and hereby agree that you are giving us your consent to track your use of this Website using Tracking Technologies, and to use Tracking Technologies in emails we send you.

Please note that you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Opting out is browser specific, meaning, if you opt out while using Safari, this choice will not affect the collection of information by Tracking Technologies when you use Internet Explorer or other web browsers. Be aware that blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full features offered on this Website. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information.

  4. ## How We Use the Information

We never sell or rent our visitors' personal information to third parties without appropriate consent. We may combine information we collect through our Website with information that we collect from other sources. On occasions we use agents or contractors to provide services to our visitors, such as helping us conduct a sweepstakes, sending prizes to winners, or providing customer service. We require agents and contractors to keep visitors’ personal information confidential and to use it only for the specific services being performed. We use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Website, and improve our visitors' experience. We also may aggregate, use and share this information with third parties to analyze Website usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services to our visitors.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a subpoena, court order or other legal process. We may also use and disclose such information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we, or one of our business units is acquired by, sold to, or merged with another entity.

We will not use or transfer personally identifiable information in ways that are materially different from the ways described above without updating this Policy.

  5. ## Collection of Information by Third-Party Websites, Ad Servers, and Sponsors

We use a variety of third-party advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers, and other service providers (collectively, “Third Party Providers”). These Third Party Providers do not have access to the information we collected about you, except to the extent necessary to provide services to this Website. For example, a Third Party Provider may require information to provide you with advertisements that interest you based on your visits to the Website and/or other sites. Third Party Providers may have their own Tracking Technologies that collect your information while you are on this Website. As such, Third Party Providers may place Tracking Technologies on the device you are using to access this Website. The use of Tracking Technologies by Third Party Providers is subject to their privacy policies and is not under our control, and therefore, where applicable, please consults the privacy policies of Third Party Providers.

  6. ## Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in an effort to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to the information we collect from you and to ensure the information is correctly used. We limit access to visitors’ information to employees, contractors, and Third Party Providers who are authorized for the proper handling of such information. Information collected from visitors of this Website will not be stored for longer than is necessary for the purposes described in this Policy.

  7. ## Children’s Privacy and Parental Review

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) requires that we inform parents and legal guardians (the “Parents”) about what personally identifiable information we collect from children under 13 years of age (the “Kid”), how we collect the information, and what we do with the information. Furthermore, COPPA requires that we obtain consent from Parents in order to allow Kids to use features of this Website that require them to provide us with personally identifiable information.

Kids can view content and use many of the Website’s services without any personally identifiable information being collected. We only collect personally identifiable information, if at all, from Kids when they provide it to us by participating in certain activities on this Website that require registration, or use Social Media Sites in connection with this Website. Such personally identifiable information may include: (1) first name; (2) last name; (3) birth date; (4) gender; (5) country of residence; (6) state (if applicable); (7) city; (8) zip code; (9) user name; (10) login password; (11) telephone number; and (12) other relevant information. When a Kid participates in an activity on this Website that requires the collection, retention, and use of personally identifiable information, we ask for the Kid’s Parent’s email address so that we can notify the Parent that we have received personally identifiable information from their Kid. For specific one-time requests we receive from Kids, email addresses are collected, but are not stored in a retrievable form, but instead stored using a “hash” or unique code generated from the email address that will allow us on a one-time basis, for example, to respond to an inquiry from the child regarding a lost user name or password. Furthermore, we never require a Kid to disclose more personally identifiably information than is reasonably necessary as a condition of participation in any Website activity.

We use Kids’ personal information for internal purposes only, such as enabling Kids to enter our online contests or sweepstakes, to subscribe to an online newsletter, to provide customer service, and/or for the purpose the information is provided. If a Kid wins a sweepstakes or contest, we notify the Parent at the Parent’s email address provided to us during the registration process and request that the Parent provide their postal address for purposes of delivering the prize. We use Parents' e-mail addresses to notify them when we have received personal information such as e-mail addresses from their Kid and to give Parents the option to remove their Kid’s name from our database. If we do not hear back from a Parent, we assume the Parent approves of the Kid providing us with personally identifiable information, and any activities the information was provided for.

If we make a material change to our Policy as it relates to Kids, we will notify Parents by email. Please make sure to update us if your email address changes, so we can notify you of such changes. We will only make material changes to our Policy in conformance with applicable law.

Please send a letter or postcard to our www.myvortexx.com Privacy Manager at the mailing address provided below if you would like to do any of the following: (1) access personally identifiable information that we have from your Kid; (2) correct factual errors in such information; (3) request to have this information deleted; or (4) request that we no longer collect or maintain such information.

Please be sure to include your e-mail address and a telephone number where we can reach you. To protect your Kid’s privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain about your Kid.

  8. ## Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Policy, and/or practices, please contact us at the following e-mail and mailing addresses:   
Email: [privacymanager@sabanbrands.com](mailto:privacymanager@sabanbrands.com)

Mailing Address:  
Privacy Manager  
Saban Brands LLC  
10100 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90026

  9. ## Updates & Effective Date

From time to time, we may update this Policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat information collected from you by noting this Policy has been updated. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Policy so that you are aware of any such updates.
